BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1845-1981, undated, Bulk: 1961-1981
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Internal, 1845-1981, undated; 2
  - Honorary Degrees, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1972-1973 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1976-1978 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1979-1981 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Honorary Degrees — Leon Jaworski, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Honors Committee, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Honors Program, 1960-1980 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Housing Regulations, 1969-1975 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Human Relations Committee, 1966, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - I Cross-Reference Sheets, 1966-1975 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Inauguration — McCall, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Inauguration — Reynolds, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Inerrancy Issue (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Inerrancy Issue (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Inerrancy Issue (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Inerrancy Issue (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Inerrancy Issue: Self Study Report of the Religion Department, Baylor University, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Institute for Oral History (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Institute of Environmental Studies, 1972-1980 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Institute of Faculty Development/Continuing Education, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Institutional Data, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Institutional Research and Testing, 1960-1981 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Insurance, 1961-1976, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Integration, 1957-1962 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Integration (1 of 2), 1963-1969 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Integration (2 of 2), 1963-1969 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Integration [Faculty Response to Secret Poll on Integration] (1 of 2), 1961 March (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Integration [Faculty Response to Secret Poll on Integration] (2 of 2), 1961 March (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Interclub Council, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Internal Auditor, 1978-1981 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - International Club, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - International Students, 1978-1981 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Investment Committee, 1965-1969 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Items [Publication], 1971 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - J Cross-Reference Sheets, 1968-1977 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - J. M. Dawson Studies in Church and State, 1975-1981 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Japan Week, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - “Jesus Christ Superstar” Production, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - John Dean Speech, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Journalism Department, 1960-1971 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Journalism Department, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Journalism Department, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Journalism Department, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Journalism Department, 1975-1977 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Journalism Department, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Journalism Department, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Kappa Sigma Chi, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Kinnard House, 1962-1964 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - KWBU-FM, 1966-1971 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - L Cross-Reference Sheets, 1963-1977 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - The Lariat, 1959-1976 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - The Lariat, 1978-1981 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Latin American Studies, 1969-1972 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Law School, 1938-1963 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Law School, 1964-1966 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Law School, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Law School, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Law School, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Law School, 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Law School, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Law School (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Law School (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Law School, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Law School (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Law School (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Law School, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Law School (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Law School (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Laurel Society [Mortar Board], 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Leakey Leadership Laboratory, 1962-1981 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Lectures, 1961-1970 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Letters to all Departments, 1974-1981 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Library, 1959-1963 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Library, 1964-1969 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Library Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Library Science Department, 1963-1972 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Literacy Center, 1962-1964 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Literacy Studies, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - M Cross-Reference Sheets, 1962-1977 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Mail Service, 1960-1973 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Margaret Fund Scholarships, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Markham Press, 1968-1980, undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Marrs McLean Science Building, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Marshall Scholarships, 1965-1972 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Master Campus Development Plan, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Mathematics Department, 1960-1974 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Mathematics Department, 1975-1981 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Maxwell Scholarships, 1960-1964 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - McCall Scholarship, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - McKnight Student Aid Fund, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Memorandums, 1961-1967 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Memorandums, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Memorandums, 1970-1971 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Memorandums, 1972-1974 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Merit Scholarships, 1965-1977 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Mexican-American Culture Program, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Mexican-American Students, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Middle East Program, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Monsanto Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Moody Foundation, 1964-1968 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Moody Foundation, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Moody Foundation, 1970-1974 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - [Moody Memorial Library] New Library, 1963-1966 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Moody Memorial Library, 1966-1968 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Moody Memorial Library, 1969-1972 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Moody Memorial Library, 1973-1975 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Moody Memorial Library, 1976-1981 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Moratorium, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - N Cross-Reference Sheets, 1967-1971 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Natural Science Building, 1962-1967 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Noze Brotherhood, 1978-1981 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - O Cross-Reference Sheets, 1969-1972 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Office Hours, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Old Buildings, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1961-1975 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Option Committee-Baylor Stadium Corporation, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Organizational Chart, 1968-1975 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Oral Communication Department, 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Oral Communication Department, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Oral Communication Department, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Oral Communication Department, 1967-1971 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Oral Communication Department, 1972-1976 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Oral Communication Department, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Oral Communication Department, 1978-1981 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Orientation, 1962-1967 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Outstanding Faculty Member, 1970-1975 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - P Cross-Reference Sheets, 1960-1977 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Parents Day/Weekend, 1962-1975 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Parents League, 1968-1972 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Penland Hall, 1960-1970 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Personnel/Payroll, 1967-1978 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Phi Alpha Delta Law Fraternity, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Phi Betta Kappa, 1962-1981 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Phi Gamma Delta, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Philosophy Department, 1960-1981 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Physical Education Department, 1963-1974 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Physical Education — Baylor Camp Recreation Center and Sports, 1975-1981 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Physical Plant, 1960-1980 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Physics, 1960-1968 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Physics, 1969-1981 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Pi Omega Pi, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Pigskin Revue, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Piper Professors, 1964-1980 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Planning Projects — Expansion and Development, circa 1960-1969 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Pledging and Physical Hazing, 1962-1968 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Poage Library, 1973-1979 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Political Science Department, 1960-1974 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Political Science Department, 1975-1981 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Power Plant, undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Prayer Breakfast, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - President’s Corporation Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Profile ’85 Campaign, 1978-1981 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Project “GAP”, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Baylor University Academic Motivation Program, undated (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - “Proposing: A Department of Photographic Services for Baylor University”, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Psychology Department, 1960-1966 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Psychology Department, 1967-1974 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Psychology Department, 1975-1977 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Psychology Department, 1978-1981 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Psi Chi, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Public Relations, 1959-1962 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Public Relations, 1963-1966 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Public Relations, 1967-1968 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Public Relations/Affairs, 1969-1981 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - R Cross-Reference Sheets, 1959-1972 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Recruiting and Counseling Center, 1967-1972 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Registrar, 1959-1962 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Registrar, 1963-1981 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Religion Department, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Religion Department, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Religion Department, 1962-1965 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Religion Department, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Religion Department, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Religion Department, 1969-1975 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Religion Department, 1975-1979 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Religion Department, 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Report of the Visiting Team, 1964 March (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Report on Entrance Examinations of Baylor Freshman, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Research Administration, 1975-1981 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Research Grants, 1963-1969 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions, 1967-1968, undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Retirement, 1961-1972 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Reserve Officers' Training Corps (R.O.T.C.), 1960-1975 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - S Cross-Reference Sheets, 1965-1978 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Sabbaticals, 1967-1977 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Samuel Palmer Brooks Memorial Scholarship, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships, 1959-1966 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Scholarships, 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - School of Communications [Proposal], 1960 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - School of Education, 1963-1968 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - School of Education, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - School of Education, 1971-1978 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - School of Education, 1979-1981 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - School of Music, 1959-1964 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - School of Music, 1965-1966 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - School of Music, 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - School of Music (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - School of Music (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - School of Music, 1970-1972 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - School of Music, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - School of Music, 1975-1977 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - School of Music, 1978-1979 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - School of Music, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - School of Nursing, 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - School of Nursing, 1961-1964 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - School of Nursing, 1965-1974 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - School of Nursing, 1975-1978 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - School of Nursing, 1979-1981 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - School of Social Work, 1959-1967 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Science Fair, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Self-Study (1 of 2), 1968-1980 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Self-Study (2 of 2), 1968-1980 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Senior Class, 1961-1974 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Sid Richardson Science Building, 1960-1967 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Sigma Omega Sigma/Tau Kappa Epsilon, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Sigma Xi, 1962-1965 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - “Sing”, 1970-1977 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Slavic Department [Proposal], 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Social Clubs, 1966, undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Sociology Department, 1960-1976 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Sociology/Anthropology/Social Work/Gerontology, 1976-1979 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Sociology/Anthropology/Social Work/Gerontology, 1980-1981 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Spanish Department, 1968-1980 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Sparkman Scholarship, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Speaker Policy, 1970-1972 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Speech-Radio Department, 1960-1973 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Statement of Purpose, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Strecker Museum, 1964-1973 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Student Administrative Intern Program, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Student Affairs/Student Life, 1967-1981 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Student Aid Society, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Student Attorney Proposal, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Student Body Constitution, undated (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Student Conduct, 1970-1977 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Student Congress/Government, 1960-1967 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Student Congress/Government, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Student Congress/Government, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Student Congress/Government, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Student Congress/Government, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Student Congress/Government, 1972-1973 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Student Congress/Government, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Student Congress/Government, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Student Congress/Government, 1976-1979 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Student Congress/Government, 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Student Government Report to the University President, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Student Development, 1977-1980 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Student Dress, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Student Employment, 1960-1976 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Student Evaluations [of Faculty], 1971 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Student Financial Aid and Placement [RESTRICTED], 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Student Financial Aid and Placement (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Student Financial Aid and Placement (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Student Financial Aid and Placement [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Student Foundation, 1970-1981 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Student Housing/Residence Halls, 1971-1981 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Student Information [Form Results of 1966 Baylor Freshman], 1966-1967 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Student Janitors, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Student Judicial Department/Legal Bureau, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Student Leadership Laboratory, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Student Officer Training, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Student Organizations Building, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Student Peace Rally, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Student Personnel Services, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Student Poll [on various topics], 1962 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Student Privacy Information, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Student Publications, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Student Reform — Chapel Reform, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Student Rights (1 of 2), 1969-1973 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Student Rights (2 of 2), 1969-1973 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Student Secretaries, 1960-1966 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Student Union Building, 1951-1977 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Student Union Building, 1978-1981 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Study Abroad, 1974-1979 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Study of Baylor Spending in the Waco Economy, 1972 Fall (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Summer Science Institute, 1960-1962 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Summer School, 1963-1977 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Summer Tour Courses, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - T Cross-Reference Sheets, 1962-1977 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Tax Sheltered Annuity Plan, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Teacher Fellowship Program, 1968-1969 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Teachers Evaluation, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Tenure, 1968-1972 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Tenure, 1973-1977 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Tenure, 1978-1981 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Testing Center, 1959-1973 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - The Texas Collection, 1962-1972 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - The Texas Collection, 1973-1977 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - The Texas Collection, 1978-1981 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Thanksgiving Service, 1975-1977 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Treasurer, 1976-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer, 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Tuition, 1965-1969 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Tutoring, 1969, undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - U Cross-Reference Sheets, 1968-1977 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - University Committees, 1968-1973 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - University Committees, 1974-1975 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - University Committees, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - University Committees, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - University Committees, 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - University Council, 1972-1977 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - University Council, 1978-1981 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - University External Affairs Committee, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - University Forum, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - University Library Committee, 1969-1976 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - University Research Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - University Senate, 1964-1975 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - University Senate, 1976-1981 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - V Cross-Reference Sheets, 1972-1973 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Vacations, 1962-1964 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Vice-President for Academic Affairs, 1979-1981 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Vice-President for Administration and Research, 1969-1970 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Vice-President for Business Affairs, 1976-1981 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Vice-President for Development, 1959-1966 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Vice-President for Development (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Vice-President for Development (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Vice-President for Development (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Vice-President for Development (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Vice-President for Development, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Vice-President for Development, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Vice-President for Development, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Vice-President for Development (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Vice-President for Development (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Vice-President for Development, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Vice-President for Development, 1974-1975 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Vice-President for External Affairs, 1980-1981 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1965-1966 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Folder 2)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Vice-President for Placement and Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Vice-President for Student Affairs, 1965-1968 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Vice-President for Student Affairs, 1969-1972 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Vice-President for Student Affairs, 1973-1977 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Vice-President for Student Affairs, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Vice-President for Student Affairs, 1979-1981 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Visiting Lectures, 1962-1966 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Voluntary Support of Education Survey, 1970-1976 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Waco Hall, 1964-1976 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Whip and Spur, 1942-1961 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Williams Farm, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - World Emphasis Week, 1966-1971 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- External, 1936-1981, undated; 3
  This series includes correspondence, reports, minutes, publications, programs, and other materials relating to institutions and organizations outside of Baylor University. Some materials are related to McCall as an individual and his interests and affiliations, while others are directly related to his presidency. This series is in average condition.
  - A Cross-Reference Sheets, 1962-1979 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Abilene Christian College, 1967-1980 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Abilene Rotary Club, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Acadia Education Foundation, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - ACCENT ACADEMIA Day, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - ACME Brick Company, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - ACT Testing, 1969-1975 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - ACTION Committee to Implement Organization for Needs, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Action Now, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Administrators Association, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Admirals of the Flagship Fleet Club, 1962-1966 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Advisory Board of Radio Free Europe, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Aeromedical Research Laboratory, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Aetna Life Insurance Company, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Aid Association for Lutherans, 1968-1970 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Air Force Academy Assembly, 1961-1975 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Air University (Department of the Air Force), 1969-1972 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Alamo Machine and Supply Company (AMSCO), 1975-1980 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Alaska Baptist Convention, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Albany Chamber of Commerce, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Alcoa Foundation, 1961-1977 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Alderson-Broaddus College, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Allied Chemical Foundation, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Allstate Foundation, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Aluminum Company of America (ALCOA), 1962-1964 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Amarillo, TX, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Amateur Athletic Union of the United States, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Amendment No. 1, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - America’s Future, Inc., 1962 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - American Alumni Council (AAC), 1962-1965 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - American Assembly/Association of Collegiate Schools of Business (AACSB), 1960-1978 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - American Association of Independent College and University Presidents, 1965-1967 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - American Association of Presidents of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1977-1980 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - American Association of School Administrators (AASA), 1961-1977 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1961-1967 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 21)